Amazon Custom lets you add customization options to your product listings, allowing customers
to personalize, configure, or assemble make-on-demand products.
Custom product orders must be fulfilled through the Merchant-Fulfilled Network, MFN, or the
Seller-Fulfilled Prime SFP program and are not eligible for fulfillment by Amazon FBA.
To register for Amazon Custom, you need an Amazon Professional Seller account.
Access the tool from the main menu in Seller Central by hovering over the Growth tab and
selecting Custom Program.
You can add and manage customizations for your listings from the Edit Customizations page.
The Amazon Custom Tool allows you to add multiple customizable areas for your product
called "surfaces".
For example, on a t-shirt, the front and back could be considered separate surfaces.
Each surface can include numerous customizations.
With specifications and parameters set by you, customers can personalize products through
text customization and image uploads, as well as choose from a drop-down list of product
attributes, input desired quantities or measurements, or enter special instructions or other information
into a text field.
For a step-by-step guide on how to list products with Amazon Custom, read our Create and Manage
Amazon Custom Listings PDF Guide in Seller University.